Union Labor Life Insurance Company Publications 5162
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union Labor Life Insurance Company Publications
1928-1962
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union Labor Life Insurance Company
5162
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Publications (documents).
Publications and reports of the Union Labor Life Insurance Company
5604320
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, November 11, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 07, 2019
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of publications and reports of the Union Labor Life Insurance Company.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5583/1: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1 5712: Burton B. Turkus Arbitration Files 5728: Railway Labor Executives' Association Additional Records
Social security -- United States.; Life insurance -- United States.; Union Labor Life Insurance Company.
5604320
- Annual financial statements, 1937-1945 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Financial Statement, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Annual Statement for the Year, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Annual Statement for the Year, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Statement of Condition, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). December 31, 1938. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Annual Statement for the Year, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Annual Statement for the Year, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Statement of Condition, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). February 28, 1941. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Statement of Condition, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). October 31, 1941. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Annual Statement for the Year, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Statement of Condition, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). April 30, 1942. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Annual Statement for the Year, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Annual Statement for the Year, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Annual Statement for the Year, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Annual report, 1960; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Annual Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). 24th: for the year ended December 31, 1960. Report of the Officers to the Thirty-Fifth Annual Meeting of Shareholders At Baltimore, Maryland, April 19, 1961. Item is in English.
- Audit reports, 1936-1945; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Auditor's Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By W. M. Deving. For the Year Ended December 31, 1935. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Auditor's Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By W. M. Deving. For the Year Ended December 31, 1937. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Auditor's Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By W. M. Deving. For the Year Ended December 31, 1938. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Auditor's Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By W. M. Deving. For the Year Ended December 31, 1945. Item is in English.
- Board of Directors' meetings and reports, 1935-1947; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Report: Board of Directors' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). April 17, 1935. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Report: Board of Directors' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). April 20, 1938. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Report: Board of Directors' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). April 19, 1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Report: Board of Directors' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). April 17, 1940. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Report: Board of Directors' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). April 16, 1941. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Report: Board of Directors' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). April 15, 1942. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Quarterly Audit Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). April 21, 1943. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Report: Board of Directors' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Quarterly Audit Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). April 19, 1944. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Report: Board of Directors' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: To All Members of the Board, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). February 23, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Quarterly Audit Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). March 31, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Report: Board of Directors' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). April 18, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Report: Board of Directors' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). April 17, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Report: Board of Directors' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). April 16, 1947. Item is in English.
- Board of Directors regular meetings, 1937-1947; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Regular Meeting: Minutes, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Board of Directors. April 21, 1937. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Regular Meeting: Agenda, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Board of Directors. April 18, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Regular Meeting: Agenda, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Board of Directors. April 18, 1945. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Regular Meeting: Minutes, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Regular Meeting: Agenda, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Board of Directors. April 17, 1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Regular Meeting: Minutes, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Regular Meeting: Agenda, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Board of Directors. April 16, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Regular Meeting: Minutes, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Board of Directors special meetings, 1934-1947; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Special Meeting: Minutes, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Board of Directors. April 18, 1934. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Special Meeting: Minutes, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Board of Directors. April 17, 1935. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Special Meeting: Minutes, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Board of Directors. April 29, 1935. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Special Meeting: Minutes, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Board of Directors. April 29, 1935. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Special Meeting: Minutes, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Board of Directors. April 15, 1936. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Special Meeting: Minutes, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Special Meeting: Minutes, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Board of Directors. April 20, 1938. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Special Meeting: Minutes, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Board of Directors. April 19, 1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Special Meeting: Minutes, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Board of Directors. April 17, 1940. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Special Meeting: Minutes, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Board of Directors. April 16, 1941. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Special Meeting: Minutes, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Board of Directors. April 21, 1943. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Special Meeting: Minutes, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By Board of Directors. April 19, 1944. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Special Meeting: Agenda, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: Special Meeting: Minutes, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: Special Meeting: Agenda, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 16: Special Meeting: Minutes, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 17: Special Meeting: Minutes, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Committee of Examinations, 1939-1944; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Examiner's Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By John P. Albert; Nathan Meyer. November 1, 1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Examiner's Report, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By John H. Coppage; E. F. Northrop. March 1, 1944. Item is in English.
- "The Company Behind the Contract", Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  no date
  - Item 1: The Company Behind the Contract, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Matthew Woll. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Company Behind the Contract, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Edmund P. Tobin. Item is in English.
- Executive Committee, 1945-1947; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Executive Committee Meeting: Agenda, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Executive Committee. April 18, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: To Directors and Executive Committee Members, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Matthew Woll. April 10, 1947. Correspondence. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Special Meeting: Agenda, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Board of Directors. Attached to Matthew Woll correspondence dated April 10, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Stockholders Meeting: Agenda, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). Attached to Matthew Woll correspondence dated April 10, 1947. Item is in English.
- Financial statements, 1943-1959; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Annual Statement, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). December 31, 1943. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Financial Statement, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). December 31, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Financial Statement, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). December 31, 1945. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: 31st Financial Statement, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). December 31, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: 31st Financial Statement, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). December 31, 1957. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: 33rd Financial Statement, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). December 31, 1959. Item is in English.
- Group insurance, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Announcement of a Plan of Group Insurance, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Wilbur-Suchard Chocolate Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Your Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By Ronson Art Metal Works. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Vote for Group Life Insurance, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Vote for Group Life Insurance, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Vote for Group Life Insurance, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). Copy 2. Item is in English.
- "Labor's Own", 1957; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Offprint from AFL-CIO American Federationist
  - Item 1: Labor's Own, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    By Edmund P. Tobin. Reprinted from AFL-CIO American Federationist, September, 1957. Item is in English.
- Leaflets, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: This Can Happen to You, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: This Can Happen to You, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: An Important Announcement to Organized Labor and Its Leaders, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: An Important Announcement to Organized Labor and Its Leaders, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Too Good To Be True, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: Gentlemen: Please send me information..., Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). Business Reply Card. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Gentlemen: Please send me information..., Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: Annual Premium Rates, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 9: Analysis Chart: The Union Labor Life Insurance Company and The Fifteen Largest Life Insurance Companies, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By Dunne's International Insurance Reports. December 31, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Growth With Security, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 11: Checking Up On You, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 12: Checking Up On You, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 13: You Have an Aladdin's Lamp, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 14: Proof, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 15: The House You Built on a Rock: Reassuring News About Your Best Property, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 16: Up the Stream, or Down the Tracks?, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 17: When Your Roof Is Damaged, Your Protection Is Impaired, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 18: Simple Facts but Important, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 19: Think It Over, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 20: The Key to Security Through Your Company, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 21: So They Can Carry On, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 22: So They Can Carry On, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 23: So They Can Carry On, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: But Take Yourself Out of the Picture!, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Low cost insurance, 1944-1945; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Low Cost Life Insurance, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Low Cost Insurance, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Report of the Officers, 1938-1940; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Our Second Decade: The First Year of Second Decade Evidences Remarkable Progress, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). Report of the Officers of the Union Labor Life Insurance Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Record of Accomplishment: Another Year of Progress, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Report of Officers, 1940-1943; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Record of Accomplishment, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Review of Year's Progress, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Our Fifteenth Anniversary, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Our Sixteenth Milestone, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Report of Officers, 1944-1946; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Accomplishment In a Trying Year, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Accomplishment In a Trying Year, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). Report of the Officers of the Union Labor Life Insurance Company. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The March of Continued Progress, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: The March of Continued Progress, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: A Review and Preview, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Retirement plan of the Union Labor Life Insurance Company, 1945; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Retirement Plan of the Union Labor Life Insurance Company, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
- "Social Security through Trade Unions", 1946; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Social Security Through Trade Unions, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Social Security Through Trade Unions, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
    By Matthew Woll. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Social Security Through Trade Unions, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Stockholders' meetings, 1928-1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Eighteenth Annual Stockholders' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Notice of Stockholders' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    By James Maloney; Matthew Woll. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Agenda for Stockholders' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: Agenda for Stockholders' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). April 18, 1945. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Nineteenth Annual Stockholders' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 6: Agenda for Stockholders' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 7: Twentieth Annual Stockholders' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 8: Twenty-First Annual Stockholders' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 9: Notice of Stockholders' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 10: To All Shareholders, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    By Matthew Woll. Correspondence. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Eighth Annual Stockholders' Meeting: Minutes, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). April 18, 1934. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Notice of Stockholders' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    By Thomas E. Burke; Matthew Woll. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Stockholder's Proxy, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 14: Ninth Annual Stockholders' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 15: T. C. Cashen, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    By Matthew Woll. Telegram. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Notice of Stockholders' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 17: Notice of Stockholders' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    By Thomas E. Burke; Matthew Woll. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Stockholder's Proxy, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 19: Tenth Annual Stockholders' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). April 15, 1936. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Notice of Stockholders' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 21: Eleventh Annual Stockholders' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). April 21, 1937. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Twelfth Annual Stockholders' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 23: Thriteenth Annual Stockholders' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 24: Fourteenth Annual Stockholders' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 25: Fifteenth Annual Stockholders' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 26: Sixteenth Annual Stockholders' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 27: Notice of Stockholders' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 28: Seventeenth Annual Stockholders' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 29: Notice of Stockholders' Meeting, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
- ULLICO Bulletin, 1946-1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: ULLICO Bulletin, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). v.1:no.9 (1946:March). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: ULLICO Bulletin, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). v.1:no.10 (1946:Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: ULLICO Bulletin, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). v.12:no.3 (1957:Apr.). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: ULLICO Bulletin, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). v.15:no.11 (1960:Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 5: ULLICO Bulletin, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
    By ULLIC (Union Labor Life Insurance Company). v.17:no.3 (1962:March). Item is in English.
- Profile of The Union Labor Life Insurance Company, 1961; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: The Union Labor Life Insurance Company, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Miscellaneous, 1928-1935; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: To Organized Labor, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: To National and International Unions, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)